{
"cards": [
    {
        "front": "How can you help integrate personas into your design & development process? ",
        "back" : "Schedule a meeting with your colleagues to introduce personas & collaborate on writing user stories",
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "When in the discovery phase, what should you think about when shaping your discovery questions?",
        "back" : "The aim and scope",
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "What research method is good for observing how participants respond questions in a group setting?",
        "back" : "Focus groups",
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "Which is the best research method to help understand what people do?",
        "back" : "Behavioral",
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "Which research method is good for grouping things into categories, for example, items in a navigation menu",
        "back" : "Card Sorting",
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "Salesforce _________ are based on users' goals, behaviors and motivations.",
        "back" : "Personas",
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "The visual representation of business processes",
        "back" : "Process Mapping",
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "What is the 'Hawthorne Effect'?",
        "back" : "The alteration of behavior by the subject of a study due to their awareness of being observed",
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "Research method that focus on what people say, is know as what?",
        "back" : "Attitudinal Method",
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "What are Qualitative Research Methods?",
        "back" : "Tries to answer 'Why?' or 'How?'",
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "What are Quantitative Research Methods?",
        "back" : "Tries to answer 'How much?' or 'How many?'",
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "When formulating discovery questions, the ___ is the intent of your work - what you are trying to find out.",
        "back" : "Aim" ,
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "When formulating discovery questions, the ___ is who you're researching and how you're doing your analysis.",
        "back" : "Scope" ,
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    {
        "front": "Observing a participant in their own environment to better understand how they work is an example of what research method?",
        "back" : "Contextual inquiry" ,
        "icon" : "record_lookup",
        "iconCol": "record-lookup",
        "category" : "Discovery",
        "filterCat": "discovery"
    },
    
    // UX Fundamentals
    

    {
        "front": "Why is it best to keep prototypes low/mid fidelity during the early states of rapid prototyping?",
        "back" : "Rapid prototyping involves quick feedback & iteration, so high fidelity would be a waste of time" ,
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "What is a key consideration for using color with accessability in mind?",
        "back" : "Ensure there is enough contrast between adjacent colors" ,
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "What feature does a screen reader user commonly use to navigate a page?",
        "back" : "Heading Structure of the page" ,
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "Two WCAG restrictions that are crucial to follow when designing animations for the web?",
        "back" : "Limited Flashing or blinking. Animations longer than 5 seconds can be stopped or paused.",
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "Meant to communicate structure of an app or web page, and focuses on function rather than visual design?",
        "back" : "A Wireframe.",
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "Preliminary version of a product or idea that lets project stakeholders test user interfaces.",
        "back" : "A Prototype.",
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "A difference between two or more elements in a composition",
        "back" : "Contrast",
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "A visual effect adding the illusion of depth, where a background moves at a different rate than the foreground?",
        "back" : "Parallax Effect",
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "In storytelling the background or setting of a story, where an introduction the hero and their current state is presented is known as what?",
        "back" : "Exposition",
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "Initial feedback is given on a prototype and the need for more is determined, what is next?",
        "back" : "Develop Interactive Prototypes.",
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "Survey questions like “tell us what you like best about this feature,” are known as what?",
        "back" : "Leading Questions",
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "What level of HTML headings should ONLY exist once on a page? ",
        "back" : "H1",
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "__________ icons and images that don't add any relevant information or functionality.",
        "back" : "Decorative",
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    {
        "front": "Icons and images that convey important information that the surrounding text doesn't.",
        "back" : "Informational",
        "icon" : "macros",
        "iconCol": "connected-apps",
        "category" : "UX Fundamentals",
        "filterCat": "uxfundamentals"
    },
    
    // HCI
    
    {
        "front": "Encouraging social connection, engagement, and values is the goal of what?",
        "back" : "Relationship Design",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "Desirability, feasibility, and viability are the focus of what design practice?",
        "back" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "Creating a consistent brand experience across distinct interactions is the focus of ____________?",
        "back" : "Service Design",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "Inclusivity, sustainability, and ethics are criteria for what?",
        "back" : "Relationship Design",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "Creative approach to solving people's problems beginning with their needs, and ends with solutions to meet those needs.",
        "back" : "Human-Centered Design.",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "The creation of consistent user or customer experiences across multiple interactions.",
        "back" : "Service Design",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "How easy it is for someone to use a product, & how much someone enjoys interacting with a product. Are concepts of what design practice?",
        "back" : "UX Design",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "Builds on both UX design & service design by focusing on more than just an individual person interacting with a product or brand...",
        "back" : "Relationship Design",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "When using design to strengthen customer relationships, what should you prioritize?",
        "back" : "In-depth, design-led research.",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "What could you create to capture user + customer feedback and suggestions?",
        "back" : "A Forum",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "What method could you use to better understand the employee journey and identify ways it can be improved?",
        "back" : "Journey Mapping",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "What is a benefit of introducing friction into the design process?",
        "back" : "To question the potential consequences of design and business choices.",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "To lead with strengthening connection.",
        "back" : "COMPASSION mindset.",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "To push ourselves to be vulnerable.",
        "back" : "COURAGE mindset.",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "To engage with clear purpose.",
        "back" : "INTENTION mindset.",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    {
        "front": "To exchange value in service of longevity.",
        "back" : "RECIPROCITY mindset.",
        "icon" : "user",
        "iconCol": "channel-programs",
        "category" : "Human-Centered Design",
        "filterCat": "hci"
    },
    // Declarative Design
    {
        "front": "A _____ is a declarative component a UX designer can use for on-boarding.",
        "back" : "Prompt.",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "What is a key topic covered in the declarative design section of the exam?.",
        "back" : "Global Elements.",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "A component that allows readers to acknowledge information without specifically completing an action.",
        "back" : "A Floating Prompt.",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "When designing a user engagement, what is the difference between the message and the purpose?",
        "back" : "The message is what you say to the user, the purpose is Why you say it.",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "To display all the products an account has purchased on a record page, what standard salesforce configuration should be considered?",
        "back" : "Create an Account to Product lookup relationship, then add a related list of products to the account record page.",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "A component that provides getting started resources the first time that users log in to Lightning Experience?",
        "back" : "Welcome Mat programmatic component",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "Use a _______ to point to a lower-level component on the page to provide tips and best practices.",
        "back" : "Popover programmatic component",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "Centralized list of tasks designed to help users onboard organizations, clouds, or features.",
        "back" : "Setup Assistant programmatic component.",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "When users may not notice or seek out help, but would benefit from assistance is an example of what method?",
        "back" : "Push Method.",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "When the user is motivated to seek help is an example of what method?",
        "back" : "Pull Method.",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "Floating and docked are examples of what type of component?",
        "back" : "Salesforce Prompts.",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "Show users where to begin and what's new or changed - the 'aha moment' is what engagement scenario?",
        "back" : "Onboarding.",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "Raising awareness of a new feature is an example of what scenario?",
        "back" : "Feature Discovery & adoption.",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "_________ provides just-in-time prompts that help users learn by doing.",
        "back" : "Troubleshooting help",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "_________ gives users the skills and information they need to get as much value as possible out of your product or application.",
        "back" : "Deeper learning",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "What option gives users quick access to common productivity tools in a fixed footer.",
        "back" : "Utility Bar",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "Field-level Help is better suited for Troubleshooting OR Deeper Learning",
        "back" : "Troubleshooting",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "The _______ provides a few key resources that your users can access from anywhere",
        "back" : "Help Menu",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    
    {
        "front": "What brings the power of learning directly into the app, enabling companies to skill up teams as they work in Salesforce.",
        "back" : "Salesforce Learning Paths",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "You can place a floating prompt in one of ____ positions on a page",
        "back" : "9",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "What does M.A.P stand for?",
        "back" : "MESSAGE (what), AUDIENCE(who), PURPOSE (why)",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "What does the FACE principle, for effective content stand for?",
        "back" : "Friendly, Accurate, Concise, Educational",
        "icon" : "task",
        "iconCol": "data-streams",
        "category" : "Declarative Design",
        "filterCat": "dd"
    },
    {
        "front": "________ allows designers to observe and record how users complete assigned tasks.",
        "back" : "Usability Testing",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "What two tools should a UX designer use to test that a webpage can be navigated without a mouse?",
        "back" : "Keyboard & Screen Reader.",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "When testing for keyboard accessability, do nonmodal dialogues need to be verified?",
        "back" : "No, nonmodal dialogues can not be navigated with a keyboard .",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "When testing for keyboard accessability, does keyboard focus need to be visible?",
        "back" : "Yes, use the keyboard to ensure focusable elements have a visual indicator.",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "When testing for keyboard accessability, all ________ must be able to receive focus",
        "back" : "Actionable Items",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "For development, user acceptance testing & training, without compromising data in production. What Salesforce feature should you use?",
        "back" : "Create a Full sandbox Org",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "Why is testing alt-text with a screen reader important?",
        "back" : "So you can find out whether your alt text was actually helpful",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "_______ is a way of evaluating site structure by asking users to find items based on the site's organization & terminology",
        "back" : "Tree Testing",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "This type of test compares only one difference, A vs B",
        "back" : "Single Variant Test",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "This type of test compares more than one difference, A vs B vs C",
        "back" : "Multi-variant Test",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "What are some of the issues an Aura accessibility test look for?",
        "back" : "Images without alt attributes | Input elements without Labels | Headings (H1, H2, ..) | Fieldset elements without legend tags",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "_______ testing gives the user a task and records whether the first place the user clicks is the correct path to accomplish the task",
        "back" : "First Click Testing",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "_______ is a way to model database tables that in a way that makes sense to humans.",
        "back" : "A data model",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "________ are objects that are included with Salesforce. Account is an example of this.",
        "back" : "Standard Objects",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "Objects that you create to store information that's specific to your company or industry are what?",
        "back" : "Custom Objects",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "Where in setup would you go to create a custom field for an object?",
        "back" : "Object Manager",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "All records need this field so you can distinguish between them.",
        "back" : "Name Field",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "This special field can hold values that automatically calculated based on some expression that you write.",
        "back" : "Formula Field",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    {
        "front": "A 15-character, case-sensitive field that's automatically generated for every record.",
        "back" : "Identity Field",
        "icon" : "stage_collection",
        "iconCol": "code-set",
        "category" : "Design Testing",
        "filterCat": "dt"
    },
    // Lightning Design System
    {
        "front": "What aspect of systems design allows you to build for multiple uses, viewpoints & structures?",
        "back" : "Scalability",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "In systems design, the most important relationship is the one between what two entities?",
        "back" : "Individual elements + Overall experience",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "Creating a record is an example of what type of design pattern?",
        "back" : "A Macrointeraction",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "A customer used lightning components, and wants a global change to their button color. What feature could they use?",
        "back" : "Styling Hooks",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "What does SLDS stand for?",
        "back" : "Salesforce Lightning Design System",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "What is a good analogy for systems design?",
        "back" : "Building a house",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "Who first coined 'User Experience?'",
        "back" : "Don Norman",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "An ________ is part of an element that people recognize and associate with the actions they can take.",
        "back" : "Affordance",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "What is a repeatable design solution to a recurring problem?",
        "back" : "A Design Pattern",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "Logging in is an example example of what type of interaction pattern?",
        "back" : "A Macrointeraction",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "________ are the controls within a page that you click, tap, or take some other action on",
        "back" : "Microinteractions",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "An aerial view of a whole city is a analogy of what type of pattern?",
        "back" : "A Macrointeraction",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "Why do designers need to be thoughtful about even tiny design decisions?",
        "back" : "To avoid a time drain on users.",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "What is an example of a design speck that might presented to an engineer ",
        "back" : "Size, color, typography, interactions, margins, padding.",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "_________ provide the values inputted when a person uses the element you are designing",
        "back" : "Interaction specifications",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "What are the 6 default interaction states?",
        "back" : "Default, Disabled, Active, Hover, Focus, Pressed",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "The SC 1.4.1 guideline in WCAG 2.0 tells us to make sure _______ are never indicated by color alone",
        "back" : "State Changes",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "One of the best ways to document a design is by including what?",
        "back" : "Do's and Don'ts",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "What are the visual design atoms of the design system called?",
        "back" : "Design token",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "_________ is a way of writing and structuring code to describe its content's structural meaning, not how it visually presents the content.",
        "back" : "Semantic Markup",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "The process of running a program that will analyse code for potential errors",
        "back" : "Linting",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "What are the 4 design principles of the Lightning Design System?",
        "back" : "Clarity, Consistency, Efficiency, Beauty",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "When using a line chart to represent data, whats the max recommended data sets (lines)",
        "back" : "Four or fewer.",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "True or false, a dot plot chart is great for very large, or dense data sets?",
        "back" : "False, smaller sparser data sets are best.",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    },
    {
        "front": "A pie chart should be use to represent how many values?",
        "back" : "Between 2 and 5",
        "icon" : "connected_apps",
        "iconCol": "agent-home",
        "category" : "Lightning Design System",
        "filterCat": "slds"
    }
]
}